Zhijiang Infinite Capacity Technology (Zhejiang) Co., Ltd., Zhejiang Yanhe Culture Technology Co., Ltd.
Strange.
This path looks like
we were just here.
We're walking in circles.
Young Master Shen,
we've walked around this forest
for three laps.
Listen to me this time. Follow me.
Watch out!
This time,
you owe me a leg.
I didn't expect
you to be so careful.
Tiger!
Run!
Who are you?
I am an officer from the Yamen. Let me go.
Two officers.
How bold of you
to trespass into the Savage Valley.
We are investigating a case.
We want to ask you, hunter.
You are familiar with the terrain around here.
We are looking for
a short and agile freak.
Can you lead the way?
The government.
I don't care about
official business.
Brother,
is this enough?
The rich dine on wine and meat,
while the poor freeze to death on the streets.
You...
Sir,
may I ask which military office
you served in before?
You actually
saw that I was a soldier.
You speak forcefully
and hold a Modao.
You must be from the Anxi Army.
Good boy.
I am from the Anxi Protectorate,
under General Li,
Colonel Li Fei.
General Li.
I've heard a lot about you.
Enough.
I'm no longer a general.
Back then,
I fought desperately on the battlefield.
In the end,
due to the struggle between the royal family and the Empress,
I was demoted and sent back to my hometown.
The government,
I distrust the most.
General,
you protected the country
and shed blood.
Your achievements,
the world remembers,
and so do the people.
The corruption of the court
shouldn't bury your character.
General,
even though you live in the forest,
you still set traps to fend off wild beasts.
To protect the people.
With this intention,
you are ten thousand times better
than those hypocrites
in the court.
Good.
With your words,
my life is not in vain.
It is the court
that let you down.
To the southwest,
there is a hidden cave.
Strange noises have been heard recently.
Maybe
it has what you are looking for.
Thank you, General Li.
This is Savage Valley.
It's getting dark, so be careful.
General,
this bear trap,
can I borrow it?
This should be the place.
How about we
come back during the day?
No.
Is that Feng Er?
It really is Feng Er.
Hurry up and save him.
The life-extending soup in this jar keeps him alive.
If he comes out now,
he will definitely die.
Someone is here.
Hide.
Old thing,
does it feel good?
I'll let you taste
my pain.
Die!
You can't die.
I'll make you wish you were dead.
Old thing.
You can't die.
Chase me.
Come on, chase me.
It's full of miasma inside.
You two are dead.
Stop looking.
It's completely blocked off.
Don't waste your energy.
If you do this,
we'll use up our oxygen faster,
and we'll die sooner.
Are we
really going to die here?
Dying with you,
I don't seem to be that scared.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
Su Yao.
Actually,
I have something to tell you.
I
am actually...
Lord Su,
Mr. Shen,
are you in there?
It's Li Meng and the others.
Are you guys okay?
Good.
Don't worry.
I will get you out.
Are you okay?
How did you find us?
Thanks to a hunter.
Yes.
It's Mr. Li.
He took the bait.
I didn't expect
after all my planning,
I'd fall into a bear trap.
Who exactly are you?
I...
am the Heaven-Swallowing Mouse Spirit.
I specialize in sucking human souls.
You are not a rat spirit.
Your name is Xu Lin.